# **Adiel Goldin**

### **₽** PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a background in transnational litigation and corporate & finance law studies in the Netherlands, I gained practical experience through internships. At a Singapore law firm, I delved into legal research, case analysis, and managed crossborder cases, enhancing communication with attorneys and clients.

Later, at a satellite company's in-house counselling department, I focused on contract drafting, compliance assessments, and debt restructuring initiatives. These experiences instilled a passion for contributing to the global community, fostering adaptability, and nurturing a collaborative approach for positive impact within the legal profession.

## WORK EXPERIENCES

#### **In-House Counsel (Internship),** *Kacific* □

Oct 2023 - present

• Skills developed: Contract drafting, compliance assessments, and corporate & finance law

Singapore, Singapore

 Led due diligence processes, facilitated A&M procedures, and assisted in debt restructuring initiatives, ensuring legal and regulatory compliance, while delivering comprehensive updates to the legal team and stakeholders

## **Legal Intern,** August Law Corporation □

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

• Skills developed: legal research, case analysis, and client communication

Singapore, Singapore

· Managed cases with multi-jurisdictional nature, conducted legal research, performed regular assessments, and provided timely updates to attorneys and clients

#### **EDUCATION**

## L.L.B. Global Law (International Business Law Minor), Tilburg University

Sep 2020 - Jun 2023

Relevant modules: Corporate & Finance Law, Transnational Contract Law, Commercial Law, and Alternative Dispute Mechanisms (Arbitration)

Tilburg, Netherlands

## **A** EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

#### Human Rights Committee, Chairperson

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

· Acquired strong leadership, interpersonal and stakeholder management skills

Tilburg, Netherlands

 Developed and maintained positive relationships with key stakeholders, including university administrators, community leaders, and human rights organizations

## Students - 4 - Students, Lead Volunteer

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

• Collaborated with a team of university students to organize and coordinate visits to high schools in Tilburg with the aim of facilitating meaningful conversations with students about current events and global issues

Tilburg, Netherlands

## (S) LANGUAGES

## Hebrew Native

**English** 

Proficient

### **Bulgarian**

**Proficient** 

adieleligoldin@gmail.com 1/1